Hilda Mason, Board of Education 136
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1
  - Career Assessment Center's 1st Annual Alumni Day, Undated (Box 182, Folder 29)
  - Annual Cadet Officer Commissioning Exercises Correspondence, 1977 (Box 182, Folder 30)
  - DC Council of Teachers of English Spring Conference, Undated (Box 182, Folder 31)
  - Creative Leadership Program Young Black Achievers Conference, 1977 (Box 182, Folder 32)
  - Proposed Amendment to By Laws, 1980 (Box 182, Folder 33)
  - Annual Meeting - School Budget Issue, 1980 (Box 182, Folder 34)
  - Peace Child's Progress - 1983 Vol. No. 1 (Box 182, Folder 35)
  - Proposed General Schedule Rates for October 1978 (Box 182, Folder 36)
  - New Federal Pay Schedule and Salaries, 1976-1977 (Box 182, Folder 37)
  - Commentary on Junior College Association Act 1-54, 1975 (Box 182, Folder 38)
  - Charles Cheng Memorial Lecture Correspondence, 1981 (Box 182, Folder 39)
  - Comments on Cadet Corps Termination Act 1-49, 1975 (Box 182, Folder 40)
  - Duke Ellington School of the Arts Commencement Exercises 1981 (Box 182, Folder 41)
  - Ward VI Report, 1981 (Box 182, Folder 42)
  - Workshp for Careers in the Arts Duke Ellington School of the Arts in Recital, 1981 (Box 182, Folder 43)
  - DC Youth Orchestra, 1981 (Box 182, Folder 44)
  - DC Federation Pamphlet, Undated (Box 182, Folder 45)
  - D.C Council Bill: Duties and Responsiblities of Advisory Neighborhood Commissions Act of, 1975 (Box 182, Folder 46)
  - Descriptive Leaflet - Council for Basic Education, Undated (Box 182, Folder 47)
  - Diagnostic Survey and Candidates Answer Questions Vote for School Board Nov. 2, 1971 (Box 182, Folder 48)
  - A Commitment to Excellence - Children's Hospital and Project Correspondence, Undated (Box 182, Folder 49)
  - CIBI National Black Parent Convention, Undated (Box 182, Folder 50)
  - Handwritten Questions, Undated (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Agreement between the Board of Education of the District of Columbia and the Washington Teachers' Union, Undated (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - Kennedy Center, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 3)
  - D.C Youth Orchestra Program, Undated (Box 183, Folder 4)
  - Washington Community Open House, Undated (Box 183, Folder 5)
  - Parent - Child Center Spingarn S.T.A.Y High School, Undated (Box 183, Folder 6)
  - Head Start is for the Handicapped Too - Recognition Meeting Invitation, 1977 (Box 183, Folder 7)
  - Invitations, 1976-1977 (Box 183, Folder 8)
  - Elect Alaire Rieffel D.C School Board Ward 2 Election Day Nov. 8th, Undated (Box 183, Folder 9)
  - In the Service of America's Children and Youth - The 1972 Annual Report of the National School Boards Association, Undated (Box 183, Folder 10)
  - D.C Black Repertory Dance Company in Workshop Performance, Undated (Box 183, Folder 11)
  - Retirement Luncheon Honoring Mrs. Marguerite Carpenter Selden, Undated (Box 183, Folder 12)
  - Columbia University Commencement Program, 1979 (Box 183, Folder 13)
  - Eductors for Hilda Mason A Gathering, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 14)
  - The Superintendent's 120 Day Report, 1974 (Box 183, Folder 15)
  - Cost Center Resolution Correspondence, 1982 (Box 183, Folder 16)
  - Seventh Annual Awards Night Program, 1981 (Box 183, Folder 17)
  - Special to Members and Friends of CCM F.A.O Schwartz Game Boutique, Undated (Box 183, Folder 18)
  - Community Union Action Bulletin 1981 (Box 183, Folder 19)
  - Duke Ellington School of the Arts Commencement Exercises, 1981 (Box 183, Folder 20)
  - Fact Sheet on the Washington Teachers' Union Board of Education Contract Negotiations, Undated (Box 183, Folder 21)
  - Info on Organization who Have Donated Materials, Undated (Box 183, Folder 22)
  - City School Board Accepts Contract Recommendations, 1979 (Box 183, Folder 23)
  - Material Inventory, Undated (Box 183, Folder 24)
  - Survey for Community Use of the Wilson Pool, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 25)
  - Community- Gram Board of Education of DC Offical Public Announcement, 1979 (Box 183, Folder 26)
  - School Board Newspaper Education, 1979 (Box 183, Folder 27)
  - The Washington Teachers' Union Strike Correspondence, 1979 (Box 183, Folder 28)
  - Newspaper Article Inventory, Undated (Box 183, Folder 29)
  - Rally for Full Employment, Undated (Box 183, Folder 30)
  - For Better Public Education Inc. Correspondence, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 31)
  - School Transit Subsidy Program, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 32)
  - A Children's Winter Fantasy - Festival of Children's Choirs, 1979 (Box 183, Folder 33)
  - The Wilson Communique - Woodrow Wilson School, 1979 (Box 183, Folder 34)
  - CCY Focus on Children and Youth, 1979 (Box 183, Folder 35)
  - Recommendation Region VI, Undated (Box 183, Folder 36)
  - Ross School Newsletter, 1979 (Box 183, Folder 37)
  - Un Nuevo Dia, Undated (Box 183, Folder 38)
  - AFT Community Union We Regret Schools May be Closed…! Why? Labor Practices, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 39)
  - Aurelia Henry Reinhardt Professorship, 1976 (Box 183, Folder 40)
  - Retirement Luncheon, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 41)
  - School Discipline: New Approaches to an Old Problem Panel Discussion Announcement, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 42)
  - United Teachers for A Reponsive Union/Caucus Platform/Contract Enforcement/Paticipatory Democracy/Teacher Self Renewal, Undated (Box 183, Folder 43)
  - National Newsletter: Table of Contents, 1977 (Box 183, Folder 44)
  - Candlelighters National Newsletter, 1977 (Box 183, Folder 45)
  - Candlelighters: Meeting Announcements, 1977 (Box 183, Folder 46)
  - Massachussets Regional Community College Thank Correspondence, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 47)
  - DC Community Archives Sign In Sheet, Undated (Box 183, Folder 48)
  - Washington Teacher - Newsletter, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 49)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 50)
  - Commentary by Wallace Terry, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 51)
  - Advisory and Learning Exchange, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 52)
  - Processing Activity, Undated (Box 183, Folder 53)
  - Central Administration Directory, 1976 (Box 183, Folder 54)
  - CPR Contact List, 1976 (Box 183, Folder 55)
  - Summary of Background information on School Closing/Phasing, Undated (Box 183, Folder 56)
  - September 1980 Newsletter of the Woodrow Wilson Home and School Association/Neighborhood School Council (Box 183, Folder 57)
  - Public Hearing: Parental Responsibilty Act of 1976 and Statement: Mrs. Mason (Box 183, Folder 58)
  - Statement of Councilman Julius W. Hobson on Parental Responsibilty Act of 1976 (Box 183, Folder 59)
  - Survey on Humanistic Studies and Gerontology, 1976 (Box 183, Folder 60)
  - Galladet College Map, Undated (Box 183, Folder 61)
  - Statement of Joel D. Joseph on Behalf of Noise, 1977 (Box 183, Folder 62)
  - Names and Addresses Related to Ashley Investment Company, 1977 (Box 183, Folder 63)
  - Mason Report, 1979 (Box 183, Folder 64)
  - Teachers Strike - 1979 (Box 183, Folder 65)
  - Board of Education Public Opinion Survey, 1979 (Box 183, Folder 66)
  - References Questions, 1974 (Box 183, Folder 67)
  - Birthday Celebration Flyer, Undated (Box 183, Folder 68)
  - 1980 Six School Brochure Correspondence, 1979 (Box 183, Folder 69)
  - File Unit List, Undated (Box 183, Folder 70)
  - Michael Cogswell, 1994 (Box 183, Folder 71)
  - Coalition of Neighborhood School Councils, 1979 (Box 183, Folder 72)
  - Honoray Patrons, 1977 (Box 183, Folder 73)
  - School Board Candidate Endorsement Poll, Undated (Box 183, Folder 74)
  - Education Daily, 1976 (Box 183, Folder 75)
  - Alton Boyer, 1975 (Box 183, Folder 76)
  - Conference/Alternative State and local Public Policies, Undated (Box 183, Folder 77)
  - Student Correspondence, 1974 (Box 183, Folder 78)
  - National Women's Political Caucus, Undated (Box 183, Folder 79)
  - Books for Today's Educator, Undated (Box 183, Folder 80)
  - Handwritten Letters/Notes, 1974 (Box 183, Folder 81)
  - Recahing Out to the Citizens of Washington DC - May 1976 (Box 183, Folder 82)
  - National Survey of Black School Board Members, Undated (Box 183, Folder 83)
  - Constituent Correspondence, 1974 (Box 183, Folder 84)
  - Evaluation of Urban Enviornment Education Program, Undated (Box 183, Folder 85)
  - Carlos M. Rosario, 1974 (Box 183, Folder 86)
  - Southern Illinois University Questionaire, 1974 (Box 183, Folder 87)
  - School Board Opinonaire Negotitations and the Curriculum, 1974 (Box 183, Folder 88)
  - Andy's Miracle Card, Undated (Box 183, Folder 89)
  - Issues and Problems Survey Questionnaire, 1974 (Box 183, Folder 90)
  - Vocational Education Program Correspondence, 1975 (Box 183, Folder 91)
  - University of Wisconsin Center Questionnaire, Undated (Box 183, Folder 92)
  - National Action for Foster Children, 1973 (Box 183, Folder 93)
  - Marie H. Reed Community Learning Center, Undated (Box 183, Folder 94)
  - Photograph Child, Undated (Box 183, Folder 95)
  - Save Our School, Undated (Box 183, Folder 96)
  - Student Council Questionnaire May 8 1978 (Box 183, Folder 97)
  - Special Services to Students and Community, Undated (Box 183, Folder 98)
  - Thank you for Contribution Programs and Newsletters, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 99)
  - Far Northeast- Southeast Council Inc., 1976 (Box 183, Folder 100)
  - School Board Selection Correspondence, 1974 (Box 183, Folder 101)
  - Homosexual Employment, 1974 (Box 183, Folder 102)
  - Public School Questionaire, 1974 (Box 183, Folder 103)
  - Howard Unviersity Questionnaire, 1975 (Box 183, Folder 104)
  - Waterside Mall, 1977 (Box 183, Folder 105)
  - Barbara Sizemore, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 106)
  - Getting Down To Business, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 107)
  - Budget Alert From Betty Ann Kane, Undated (Box 183, Folder 108)
  - Bus Only - Student Livesi n Maryland, Undated (Box 183, Folder 109)
  - Two W Congress and Proposal to the National Alliance for the Arts Correspondence, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 110)
  - Economic Development for Minorities Breakfast with Jesse Jackson, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 111)
  - DC Plans for a New School Hit, 1980 (Box 183, Folder 112)
  - Hawthorne School Agreement Termination Correspondence, 1978 (Box 183, Folder 113)
  - Annual Budget Process, 1977 (Box 183, Folder 114)
  - Board of Education of D.C, 1972 (Box 183, Folder 115)
  - Captial Outlay Request For FY 1973, 1971 (Box 183, Folder 116)
  - Loyejoy- Edmond Peittion, 1971 (Box 183, Folder 117)
  - Older Schools Remark, 1972 (Box 183, Folder 118)
  - Revised FY 1973 Captial Budget, 1971 (Box 183, Folder 119)
  - Capital Improvements Program Summary, 1972 (Box 183, Folder 120)
  - National Captial Planning Commission Proposal, 1972 (Box 183, Folder 121)
  - Report of the Superintendent Budget Sketches, 1972 (Box 183, Folder 122)
  - Subcommittee on Captial Improvements Budget, 1974 (Box 183, Folder 123)
  - Pamela D. Siekmann, Undated (Box 183, Folder 124)
  - Legislative Program for the D.C Public Schools during 1975-1976-1977 (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Program for rhe D.C Public Schools during 1976 (Box 184, Folder 2)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Adams Community School, 1972 (Box 184, Folder 3)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Cleveland Elemetary School, 1974 (Box 184, Folder 4)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Bell Vocational High School, 1973 (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Survey of the Elementary School of Ward I, 1972 (Box 184, Folder 6)
  - An Overview of War One School Needs, 1972 (Box 184, Folder 7)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Amidon Elementary School, 1974 (Box 184, Folder 8)
  - Focus on Ward II - Innovation Profile, 1972 (Box 184, Folder 9)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Amidon Elementary School, 1972 (Box 184, Folder 10)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Western High, 1974 (Box 184, Folder 11)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Martin Luther King Ave, 1975 (Box 184, Folder 12)
  - Fire at Washington Highlands Elementary School, 1975 (Box 184, Folder 13)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Anacostia Preschool, Undated (Box 184, Folder 14)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Birney School, 1973 (Box 184, Folder 15)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Frederick Douglass Junior High School, Undated (Box 184, Folder 16)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Friendship Elementary School, Undated (Box 184, Folder 17)
  - School Operational and Program Profile M.V Leckie Elementary School, Undated (Box 184, Folder 18)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Anacostia Pre-School, Undated (Box 184, Folder 19)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Johnson Junior High School, Undated (Box 184, Folder 20)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Birney Elementary School, Undated (Box 184, Folder 21)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Abram Simon Elementary School, Undated (Box 184, Folder 22)
  - School Operational and Program Profile McGogney Elementary School, Undated (Box 184, Folder 23)
  - School Operational and Program Profile James A. Garfield, Undated (Box 184, Folder 24)
  - School Operational and Program Profile W.B Patterson Elementary School, Undated (Box 184, Folder 25)
  - School Operational and Program Proile M.V Leckie Elementary School, Undated (Box 184, Folder 26)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Hendley Elementary School and Annex I, Undated (Box 184, Folder 27)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Nichols Avenue Follow Through Program, Undated (Box 184, Folder 28)
  - School Operational and Program Profile A. Kiger Savoy Elementary and Annex, Undated (Box 184, Folder 29)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Anita J. Turner Elementary School, Undated (Box 184, Folder 30)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Draper Elementary School, Undated (Box 184, Folder 31)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Frank W. Ballou High School, Undated (Box 184, Folder 32)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Congress Heights Elementary, Undated (Box 184, Folder 33)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Lucy Ellen Moten Elementary School, Undated (Box 184, Folder 34)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Mildred Green Elementary School, Undated (Box 184, Folder 35)
  - School Operational and Program Profile McCogney Elementary School, Undated (Box 184, Folder 36)
  - Ward VII James E. Coates, Undated (Box 184, Folder 37)
  - Assistance to War 8 Schools from Department of Elementary Supervision, Undated (Box 184, Folder 38)
  - Kingergarten Korrespondence Mini-Kourse, Undated (Box 184, Folder 39)
  - Supplement Afro-American History, 1972 (Box 184, Folder 40)
  - Timely Teaching Tips, 1972 (Box 184, Folder 41)
  - New Directions in State and Local Tax Reform, 1977 (Box 184, Folder 42)
  - New Directions in State and Local Tax Reform, 1977 (Box 184, Folder 43)
  - Superintendent's Statement for Ward III Meeting December 5 1973 Woodrow Wilson High School (Box 184, Folder 44)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Deal Junior High School, 1973 (Box 184, Folder 45)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Eaton Elementary School, 1973 (Box 184, Folder 46)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Alice Deal Junior High, 1972 (Box 184, Folder 47)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Namie D. Lee School, 1972 (Box 184, Folder 48)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Barnard Elementary School, 1975 (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - School Operational and Program Profile Barnard Elementary School, 1974 (Box 185, Folder 2)
  - School Operational and Program Profiles Ward IV, 1972 (Box 185, Folder 3)
  - Superintendent's Statement for War V Meeting February 6 1974 Phelps Vocational High School (Box 185, Folder 4)
  - School Operational and Program Profiles Ward V, 1974 (Box 185, Folder 5)
  - School Operational and Program Profiles Ward VI, 1973 (Box 185, Folder 6)
  - School Operational and Program Profile VII, 1973 (Box 185, Folder 7)
  - Cuno H. Rudolph Elementary School Assessment, Undated (Box 185, Folder 8)
  - Black and White - Six Stories from a Troubled Time, 1968 (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - Urban Institute in Science and Reading Catholic University, Undated (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - Title I Comprehensive Program ESEA, 1974 (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - Commonwealth of Massachusetts Proposed Special Education Regulation\ 1974 (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - The Community is Teacher - National Institute of Education Department of Health Education and Welfare, 1976 (Box 186, Folder 5)
  - An Experience Based Career Education Program for Students in the Comprehensive High Schools of DC, 1976 (Box 186, Folder 6)
  - An Experience Based Career Education Program for Students in the Comprehensive High Schools of DC, 1977 (Box 186, Folder 7)
  - Annual Program Plan for Adult Education FY '77, 1976 (Box 186, Folder 8)
  - Justificiations for the 1977 DC Budget, 1976 (Box 186, Folder 9)
  - Brightwood - Through the Year, 1974 (Box 186, Folder 10)
  - DC Advisory Counicl on Vocational Education 5th Annual Report, 1974 (Box 186, Folder 11)
  - What Can be Done to Improve the Management of Money and Staff?, 1976 (Box 186, Folder 12)
  - Consumer Education Curriculum Guide for D.C. Public Schools, 1975 (Box 186, Folder 13)
  - Summary Report - Activities and Accomplishmentsof the Office of Planning Research and Evaluation for 1974-1975 (Box 186, Folder 14)
  - A Study of Comparative Data in Eight Large City School Systems FY 1974 AND FY 1975 (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - DC Board of Education Five Proposals, 1976 (Box 187, Folder 2)
  - GAO Report Correspondence, 1976 (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - The Community at the Bargaining Table, 1975 (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - Boundary Report for the 1973-1974 School Year (Box 187, Folder 5)
  - Report to the Congress by the Comptroller General of the United States, 1975 (Box 187, Folder 6)
  - Directory of Services for Handicapping Conditions Information Center for Handicapped Children, 1972 (Box 187, Folder 7)
  - Directory of Services for Handicapping Conditions Information Center for Handicapped Children, 1972 (Box 187, Folder 8)
  - Public Schools of DC Data Resource Book - 1973-1974 (Box 187, Folder 9)
  - High School of the Arts Proposal- May 1974 (Box 187, Folder 10)
  - The Webster School, 1968 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - Report on Webster Girl's Junior Senior High School 1968-1969 and 1969-1970, 1968-1970 (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - Program Outputs of Webster - Girls Junior Senior High School, 1969 (Box 188, Folder 3)
  - 1971 - 1972 School Year Referrals/Admissions/Discharges (Box 188, Folder 4)
  - Multi-Discpilinary Inter-Agency Approach to the Problems of School Age Pregnant Girls - 1970-1971 School Year, Undated (Box 188, Folder 5)
  - Lansing School District - 1971-1972 (Box 188, Folder 6)
  - Evaluation of a Public School Program Pregnant Girls, 1966 (Box 188, Folder 7)
  - Mini Things By Mini People, Undated (Box 188, Folder 8)
  - Randall Curriculum Guide, 1976-1977 (Box 189, Folder 1)
  - FY 1979 Operating and Capital Budgets, 1977 (Box 189, Folder 2)
  - The Commonwealth of Massachussets Department of Education, 1974 (Box 189, Folder 3)
  - The FY 1973 Preliminary Operating Budget, 1972 (Box 189, Folder 4)
  - The FY 1973 Preliminary Operating Budget Details by Program Positions and Amounts (Box 190, Folder 1)
  - The FY 1973 Preliminary Operating Budget, 1972 (Box 190, Folder 2)
  - The FY 1973 Preliminary Operating Budget (1 of 2), 1972 (Box 190, Folder 3)
  - The FY 1973 Preliminary Operating Budget (2 of 2), 1972 (Box 190, Folder 4)
  - Transcript of Record of Proceedings, 1972 (Box 190, Folder 5)
  - Title I Budget Supplement FY '75, 1974 (Box 190, Folder 6)
  - DC State Plans for Vocational Education 1974 (Box 190, Folder 7)
  - Chronology of A Problem, 1974 (Box 190, Folder 8)
  - National School Boards Ass'n (1 of 4), 1972-1974 (Box 190, Folder 9)
  - National School Boards Ass'n (2 of 4), 1972-1974 (Box 190, Folder 10)
  - National School Boards Ass'n (3 of 4), 1972-1974 (Box 190, Folder 11)
  - National School Boards Ass'n (4 of 4), 1972-1974 (Box 190, Folder 12)
  - Budget Summaries and Data (1 of 2), 1972-1974 (Box 190, Folder 13)
  - Budget Summaries and Data (2 of 2), 1972-1974 (Box 190, Folder 14)
  - Hobson v Hobson June 19 1967 (Box 190, Folder 15)
  - Board Vacancy Applicants (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - Board Vacancy Applicants (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - Reading Improvement Program Guines, 1972-1976 (Box 191, Folder 3)
  - Sequential Levels of Reading Skills, Undated (Box 191, Folder 4)
  - Reading Comprehension Skills, 1971 (Box 191, Folder 5)
  - Pupil Personnel Services Annual Reports 1974-1975, Undated (Box 191, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report - 1974-1975, Undated (Box 191, Folder 7)
  - Division of Pupil Personnel Services 1972-1973, Undated (Box 191, Folder 8)
  - Department of Pupil Personnel Services Annual Report 1971-1972, Undated (Box 191, Folder 9)
  - Department of Pupil Personnel Services Annual Report 1970-1971, Undated (Box 191, Folder 10)
  - Joint Center for Political Studies (1 of 6), 1972-1976 (Box 191, Folder 11)
  - Joint Center for Political Studies (2 of 6), 1972-1976 (Box 191, Folder 12)
  - Joint Center for Political Studies (3 of 6), 1972-1976 (Box 191, Folder 13)
  - Joint Center for Political Studies (4 of 6), 1972-1976 (Box 191, Folder 14)
  - Joint Center for Political Studies (5 of 6), 1972-1976 (Box 191, Folder 15)
  - Joint Center for Political Studies (6 of 6), 1972-1976 (Box 191, Folder 16)
  - WMAL, 1972-1975 (Box 191, Folder 17)
  - WRC - TV Editorials, 1972-1977 (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - Board Operation Rules ( 1 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - Board Operation Rules ( 2 of 2), 1974-1975 (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Preliminary Estimates of Speical Fund Revenues and Expenditures for FY 1972-1973 (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - W.T.O.P Editorials, 1972-1976 (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - DC Youth Orchestra (1 of 3), 1970-1980 (Box 192, Folder 6)
  - DC Youth Orchestra (2 of 3), 1970-1980 (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - DC Youth Orchestra (3 of 3), 1970-1980 (Box 192, Folder 8)
  - File Unit List, Undated (Box 192, Folder 9)
  - Homeroom Sign in Sheet, Undated (Box 192, Folder 10)
  - Notice of Public Hearing on School, 1980 (Box 192, Folder 11)
  - Bill 398 Surplus Public School Building Disposal Act of 1980 (Box 192, Folder 12)
  - Dupont Circle Advisory Neighborhood Commission Correspondence, 1980 (Box 192, Folder 13)
  - Summer Renovation Correspondence, 1980 (Box 192, Folder 14)
  - American Education Magazine, 1970 (Box 192, Folder 15)
  - Opinion Regarding the Authority of the Mayor and Council to Reprogram Capital Improvement Funds, 1978 (Box 192, Folder 16)
  - DC Association for Supervision and Curriculum Reception, 1980 (Box 192, Folder 17)
  - New Member Correspondence, 1981 (Box 192, Folder 18)
  - Proposed Amendment to By Laws, 1980 (Box 192, Folder 19)
  - Ambrosia T. Shepherd, 1973 (Box 192, Folder 20)
  - Follow Through Newsletter - 1970-1971 (Box 192, Folder 21)
  - H.R 9488/8683/6273/9258, 1971 (Box 192, Folder 22)
  - Planning Parent - Implemented Programs, Undated (Box 192, Folder 23)
  - Candidacy for Membership on the Board of Education Ward IV, 1977 (Box 192, Folder 24)
  - The Board of Education Vacancy Election Act of 1977 (Box 192, Folder 25)
  - Emergency Legislation Comments, Undated (Box 192, Folder 26)
  - Community - Gram Official Public Announcement, 1977 (Box 192, Folder 27)
  - Mason Resignation Correspondence, 1977 (Box 192, Folder 28)
  - Pupil Peronnel Services Satellite Project Evaluation for Academic Year 1973-1974 (Box 192, Folder 29)
  - Executive Office of the Commissioner Financial and Statistical Report - 1971, 1970 (Box 192, Folder 30)
  - Congressional Record Vol. 121, 1975 (Box 192, Folder 31)
  - Education Vouchers: A Report on Elementary Education By Grants to Parents December - 1970 (Box 192, Folder 32)
  - Education Vouchers, 1971-1974 (Box 192, Folder 33)
  - 4th Special Meeting, 1976 (Box 192, Folder 34)